we use the internet for everything to
我们使用互联网做一切事情,
talk to our loved ones to work together
像跟喜欢的人聊天来一起工作,
play together the wonder of the web is
一起玩耍. 网络的奇迹是
that people have participated in the
人们参与的
last 25 years sharing so much about
在过去的 25 年共享如此多的关于他们自己.
themselves but unfortunately we built it
但不幸的是我们构建他的基础
on a very fragile infrastructure we have
是在一个非常脆弱的基础设施. 我们拥有呈现指数增长的
this exponential growth in the amount of
数量的
data generated and in that data that
生成的数据并且这些数据
means to store and safeguard the way the
意味着需要存储和保护.
Internet has evolved there are single
互联网的发展已经演变为到处单点故障.
points of failure everywhere we saw this
我们发现这个发生
play out in Egypt where suddenly one
在埃及突然
morning people woke up to the internet
一个早上, 人们醒来, 互联网刚刚完全关闭.
just completely shut down they can reach
互联网刚刚完全关闭. 他们不能接触彼此, 不能跟彼此说话.
each other they couldn't talk to each
他们不能接触彼此, 不能跟彼此通话.
other we believe is incredibly important
我们认为这是非常的重要
to improve the properties of the
去改善互联网的属性.
internet with the ideas of
通过
decentralization and peer-to-peer
去中心化和点对点
knowledge so that's what we're working
知识, 这就是我们正在研究的.
on we built ipfs a protocol to remove
我们构建了 IPFS 一个协议来删除
those central points of failure to
那些中心的单点失败问题
improve the resilience of the internet
来提高互联网和网页的弹性,
and the web and to give information a
并给出信息关于
stronger sense of permanence a ipfs is a
更强的持久化. IPFS 是一个
really amazing community of developers
真正的惊人的开发者社区
that are interested in building to
有兴趣构建
centralize technology I fast as a
去中心化技术.
large-scale open-source endeavor with
有大规模开源志愿者
people that contribute from all over the
来自全世界的人
world we are a community of people who
我们是一个社区
really care about the future of the web
人们真正关心网页的未来
and who want to address the problems
和那些想要查出问题的人
feels to us like the web is
对于我们来说, 网页是
consolidating at the applications layer
在应用层合并
around a small number of data monopolies
很多小的数据文件组成的.
and we're really big believers in the
并且我们确实强烈相信
Reda centralization of that wonderful
重新去中心化那些精彩的
resource and when we first met one we
资源, 并且当我们第一次
realized that what he was doing is one
意识到他正在做的可能是
of the real keys to making that possible
使这个成为可能的真正的关键之一
[Music]
[音乐]
the first phase of our work
我们工作的第一阶段
decentralizing the web was to build ipfs
去中心化网页是构建 IPFS.
the next phase improving on this
下一个阶段改善这个基础
foundation is a new protocol bachlin
是一个新协议 Filecoin.
with the rise of protocols like Bitcoin
随着比特币和以太坊等协议的兴起
and aetherium we've seen massive
我们看到了大量的
decentralized networks form where anyone
去中心化网络形式, 在这任何人
can dedicate their computer to run the
可以用他们的电脑来运行
network and earn crypto tokens for doing
这个网络为了获得加密 token 来这么做.
so mining for tokens is so profitable
所以挖掘 token 是如此有利可图
that these networks have spreaded
以至于这些网络向全球扩散
globally and created the world's most
并且创建了全世界最
powerful computing systems we realized
强大的计算系统. 我们意识到了
that we could use the same kind of
我们可以使用相同类型的
incentive structures of Bitcoin to
比特币的激励结构
create a decentralized storage network
创建一个去中心化的存储网络
there is a massive amount of unused
有大量的未使用的
latent storage out there the vision for
存储潜藏在那里. Filecoin 的愿景是
file claim is to create a decentralized
创建一个去中心化的
storage market and networks kind of like
存储市场.
Airbnb where all that unused storage can
一个类似 Airbnb 的网络, 所有未使用的存储可以
be sold on the market so with this vast
在市场上出售. 因此, 随着这样大量的
amount of supply joining the network
供应加入网络
that is not currently connected we can
当前并没有被连接到网络. 我们可以
optimize our resources and drop the cost
优化我们的资源, 来降低存储的成本
of storage one of the key things about
Filecoin 网络的一个关键是
the Casa network is that there is a
有一个
native token to the system and that's
原生的 Token 系统, 这就是 Filecoin.
the fostering it's the medium of
它是一种媒介来促成
exchange for this decentralized market
这个去中心化的市场交易.
users spend filing to hire the network
用户花费 Filecoin 来雇佣网络来
to store their files and storage
存储他们的文件. 并且存储
providers get paid in South Point which
提供者以 Filecoin 的形式获得收益.
scales with how much storage they add
这个收益取决于他们添加多少存储
and how close they are to the users one
以及他们离用户多近.
of the powerful things about file coin
一件关于 Filecoin 的强大的事情是
is that it allows individuals to be
它允许个人成为
incentivized to act as parts of a
以物质激励来作为网络的一部分.
network each individual will contribute
每一个个人将会贡献
their part and get paid for it but then
他们的部分并且因此获得收益. 但是那时
the sum of all the individuals will
所有个人的总和将会
create a network that it's much more
创建一个网络, 那会是比我们
powerful than the systems that we have
现在拥有的网络强大的多.
today PowerPoint can be exchanged for
Filecoin 可以和比特币,
Bitcoin aetherium dollars euros and so
以太坊, 美元, 欧元等等进行交易.
on or users can hold on to their pal
或者用户可以保留 Filecoin 等到网络增长时增值.
coin which may appreciate as the network
等到网络增长时增值.
grows anybody who uses the technology
任何人使用这项技术
can become an investor in the technology
可以成为这个技术的投资者
they can buy tokens
他们可以购买 Token
that file coin is successful they can
Filecoin 是成功的
share in that financial success it's
他们可以分享这个财务成功.
kind of like anybody in the world being
他有点类似于世界上任何人都能够
able to get a seed investment in a
获得一个种子投资
Google or a Facebook or an Amazon or
给 Google 或 Facebook 或 亚马逊
something like that
或者其他类似的公司.
Falcone is going to completely reimagine
Filecoin 将完全重新设想
the way data is stored and delivered
数据存储和分发的方式
especially in the places where internet
尤其是在互联网
service is most fragile just like people
服务脆弱的地方. 就像人们在全世界
mined Bitcoin all over the world local
挖矿比特币一样.
entrepreneurs will realize they can mine
本地的企业家会意识到他们可以挖矿
pal coin by plugging together as many
Filecoin 通过把他们能得到的尽可能多的硬盘插入到一起
card drives as they can get not only can
他们不仅仅可以
they earn significant amounts of money
赚取大量的钱
but they can also provide a valuable
但他们也可以提供有价值的服务
service to their local community we can
给他们本地的社区. 我们可以
move all of the really valuable precious
移动所有的真正有价值的
content of the Internet this amazing
互联网内容, 通过这个惊人的技术
compendium of knowledge into those
到我们
regions so we can be served locally and
可以本地服务的区域.
give access to billions of people who
并且给数十亿当前被互联网封锁的人
are currently locked out of the web
访问.
[Music]
[音乐]
you
您